# Moaaz Hail Nasr-Eldeen Elshahed

## Software Engineer

0111872226 hailmoaaz@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/moaaz-al-shahed-890a2820b/

Cairo/Egypt

Recent graduate with a Bachelor's degree in Computer & Artificial Intelligence. Developed an AI model using CNN during my final year project, improving user experience for a local library. Possesses strong problem-solving skills and a desire to excel in the software industry.

## **EDUCATION**

### **Modern University for Technology and Information (MTI)**

(Aug 2021-Jun 2024)

Bachelor's degree in Computer & Artificial Intelligence | GPA: 2.6 / 4.0

## **SKILLS**

## **Programming languages:**

- C++, C#, C, Python, JavaScript, prolog, SQL

## **Concepts:**

- Object Oriented Programming -Algorithms -Data Structure

#### Libraries:

- Keras, Tensorflow, os, pandas, matplotlib, numpy, pygame, Tkinder

#### Frameworks:

- Windows form application ,ASP.net ,React.js ,Bootstrap, Open GL

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Information Technology Institute (ITI)**

(Aug 2023-Sep 2023)

Embedded System | Internship

- C programming, Embedded System concept, AVR Interface
- Made Stop watch project
- Made Clinic Management System project

#### **ZEWAIL CITY & IMPACT**

(Aug 2023-Jan 2024)

Artificial Intelligence (AI) | Internship

- Python programming, introduction to AI
- Neural Network, Support Vector Machines (SVM)

## Language

Arabic: Native | English: Intermediate